

PROFILE

Business analyst focused on the Information Technology area, with a extensive experience, from analysis and evaluation of existing systems.

I believe that the good management of systems departments can contribute greatly to companies both in the implementation of projects and in the solution of the various situations that may arise during its development.

CONTACT

PHONE (899)3-417897

WEBSITE El sitio web va aquí

EMAIL

gloria isabel@hotmail.com

HOBBIES

Movies TV Shows Listen to music Walk/Running

GLORIA ISABEL HERNANDEZ MACIAS

Master of IT Management

EDUCATION

Tecmilenio University

2013 - 2015

Title: Master in Information Technology Management

Universidad Autónoma de Tamaulipas

2006 - 2010

Title: Bachelor of Computer Systems Engineering

Centro de Estudios Tecnológicos y de Servicios No. 131

2003 - 2006

Title: Computer Technician

GRADUATES

Bronze Six Sigma Certified

iQor Global Services

Local Area Networks

Universidad Autónoma de Tamaulipas

Object Oriented Programming with Java (NetBeans IDE)

Universidad Autónoma de Tamaulipas

WORK EXPERIENCE

Reynosa Municipal Services Administration Center, Tamps. | Planning and monitoring

March 2021 - Present

Route planning for waste collection units useless.

Map position monitoring of these units..

Telephone attention to citizen reports..

AvenaSoft | Freelance

March 2021 – Present Logo design. Project manager.

Autonomous University of Tamaulipas | Teacher

August 2019 - December 2020

Free time teacher in the following subjects:

- Algorithm Analysis
- Programation advance
- SQL Server

iQor Global Services de México | Business Analyst II

March 2017 - January 2021

Coordinate development tasks.

Create, review or edit project documentation.

Schedule project initiation and follow-up meetings.

Create flowcharts.

Keep projects on time.

Test tracking before and after change deployments.

Create Test Case Files.

Keep communication active.

Follow-up and assignment of activities with programmers, clients and operations.

iQor Global Services de México | Systems Analyst II

January 2012 - March 2017

Software development and optimization (Java).

Analyze and design solutions for the organization's system.

Develop queries in SQL.

Collaborate with project manager.

Analysis, correction and monitoring of system errors.

System administrator.

User account manager.

Project planning.

Jabil Global Services de México | Systems Analyst I

January 2011 - January 2012

Capture, manipulation and analysis of information for the generation of reports.

Create Reports.

Generate process path scheme.

Audit user accounts.

Changes to the production system according to requirements.

Installation and configuration of Laser and Zebra Printers.

APTITUDES

Teamwork.

Proactivity.

Leadership.

Information analysis and decision making.

Project management.

Analysis, evaluation and development of Systems.

Development of database queries and objects.

User administration.

End user support.

Hardware and computer equipment installation.

LAN fault tracking.

Analysis and distribution of signal in wireless networks

LENGUAJES

- Español (Nativo)
- English (Limited Working)